<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>North County Real Estate Careers</title>
    <description>Jim Crotwell, a top Real Estate Agent in Orange County, shares his own internal real estate agent training for free. His Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 15:47:59 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 15:47:59 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Keller Williams Command: Built by Agents, for Agents</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/0sJSR90nFv4?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The way an agent markets themselves is essential to their business, but properly developing and executing one’s marketing strategy isn’t always so simple. This is where Keller Williams Command comes in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keller Williams Command is an end-to-end marketing platform built by and for real estate agents.&lt;/strong&gt; This one-of-a-kind tool utilizes everything agents have been asking for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of this platform’s features is Sketchhouse Designs: our marketing warehouse, which allows agents to view, customize, and save designs that can be used on social media, email campaigns, text campaigns, on your website, or ordered for print. This is hugely beneficial, as using consistent designs throughout these various mediums will boost the productivity of your marketing. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=This platform gives you the tools to reach your database, while also guiding you on the most effective ways to do so.%20http://localhost:4000/keller-williams-command-built-by-agents-for-agents.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“This platform gives you the tools to reach your database, while also guiding you on the most effective ways to do so.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only does Sketchhouse Designs give you access to all of your marketing designs with just a few clicks, but it also grants you the ability to take advantage of another tool—lead accelerator, which lets you boost designs on social media. Better still, you can do so without paying a middle party. This will give you more clicks and leads for your dollar than on Facebook or Google ads, thanks to the fact that you’re working straight from one convenient source. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And since the entire Keller Williams Command platform works off of AI, it constantly learns from user input. Over time, the platform records trends on what techniques, marketing mediums, and designs perform the best, and will show you rankings for all of the marketing elements you employ. In short, this platform gives you the tools to reach your database, while also guiding you on the most effective ways to do so. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You can learn more about this platform, and other pieces of KW technology, by visiting&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://technology.kw.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;technology.kw.com&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, if you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 11:27:15 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/keller-williams-command-built-by-agents-for-agents.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/keller-williams-command-built-by-agents-for-agents.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What “Opportunities” Can Do for You</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/EfPfwOpXoNE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is the new “Opportunities” app in KW Command and what can it do for you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Opportunities, &lt;strong&gt;y&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ou can navigate the first conversation you have with a client all the way to closing and getting paid all on one screen.&lt;/strong&gt; Also, it calculates pending commission, possible commission, and actual commission based on your true work percentages for your conversion rates from beginning to closing, and it reminds you of follow-ups and tasks and keeps compliance and pay items in the same place. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason so many agents are excited about Opportunities is it enhances the motivation for follow-ups by letting you see the dollar amount attached. While watching the transaction step by step from beginning to end, you can see your money go from potential income to probable income to actual income.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=The reason so many agents are excited about Opportunities is it enhances the motivation for follow-ups by letting you see the dollar amount attached.%20http://localhost:4000/what-opportunities-can-do-for-you.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“The reason so many agents are excited about Opportunities is it enhances the motivation for follow-ups by letting you see the dollar amount attached.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On top of that, it tracks your business (how much of it is listings, how much of it is&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;sales, how much of it is leases, etc.) and where that business comes from. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you’d like to test “Opportunities” for yourself and see what it can do, visit &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://technology.kw.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Technology.KW.com&lt;/a&gt;. If you have any more questions about this app, give us a call and we’d be happy to walk you through it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, if there’s anything else we can assist you with, feel free to reach out to us as well. We look forward to speaking with you. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 08:41:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-opportunities-can-do-for-you.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/what-opportunities-can-do-for-you.html</guid>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We’d Love to See You at Our Upcoming Lead Generation Course</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/lJ_l5f3fR3w?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve got a whole list of events coming up this September, and you won’t want to miss the one I’m unveiling today: &lt;strong&gt;On Thursday, September 12, the one and only Gene Rivers will be teaching an all-day course on lead generation. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re not familiar with Gene and his story, let me fill you in. He has four offices in Florida and along the East Coast with over 500 Keller Williams agents working under him. For more than 20 years, he and his wife have had their own mega-production, top-producing team. He also owns an escrow company as well as an investment company. Now, he spends a lot of his time traveling across the country and teaching at various Keller Williams offices.    &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=On September 12, we’ll delve deeper into new ways and strategies to improve your lead generation.%20http://localhost:4000/wed-love-to-see-you-at-our-upcoming-lead-generation-course.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“On September 12, we’ll delve deeper into new ways and strategies to improve your lead generation.”&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This event on September 12 is open to all agents in the area, and we expect a few hundred people to attend. &lt;strong&gt;It’ll run from 9 a.m. to 5 p.m. and will be held at The Westin Carlsbad, located at 5480 Grand Pacific Drive. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, let me ask you a question: What was the last class you attended at your office? A contracts class? Perhaps it was a broker update. The reason I ask is that a lot of the material that offices and brokerages teach concerns the transactional side of the business. That’s all well and good, but in my view, there’s a lack of emphasis and education on the business generation side. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Basically, your business can be broken down into three categories: lead generation, lead follow-up, and transacting. They’re all equally important, but on September 12, &lt;strong&gt;we’ll delve deeper into new ways and strategies to improve your lead generation. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What we won’t do is overwhelm you with 50 different strategies and wish you luck in implementing all of them. We’ll do two things instead: First, &lt;strong&gt;w&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;e’ll underscore two or three strategies to work into your business,&lt;/strong&gt; which will help maximize your lead generation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Secondly, &lt;strong&gt;we’ll talk a lot about follow-up&lt;/strong&gt;—how to do it and when to do it. If you lack strong follow-up skills, I can guarantee you’re leaving money on the table and missing opportunities for business.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can find out more information or register for this event &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eventbrite.com/e/lead-generation-wgene-rivers-tickets-63936199895&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll receive some information via email from me soon, but in the meantime, make a note of this event on your calendar and reach out to me with any questions you have. I hope to see you there! &lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 04:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/wed-love-to-see-you-at-our-upcoming-lead-generation-course.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/wed-love-to-see-you-at-our-upcoming-lead-generation-course.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Will You Join Us for Our Next Mastermind?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/yIucJmykh3o?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;present-before-paste present-before-paste&quot;&gt;Today I’d like to just take a moment to tell you about some great panels and other events that we’ve got coming up. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;present-before-paste&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One is our Top Producer Mastermind, where we invite three or four of our top agents and one outside agent to discuss a monthly topic.&lt;/strong&gt; These have been really powerful over the last few months. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;present-before-paste&quot;&gt;The first one we did was about client events and what people are doing in that arena. A few top producers shared what they did, ranging from expensive dinner parties to cheaper events that can still make an impact in the community. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;present-before-paste&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=These masterminds have been really powerful.%20http://localhost:4000/will-you-join-us-for-our-next-mastermind.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“These masterminds have been really powerful.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;present-before-paste&quot;&gt;The second mastermind covered the topic: “How to become the local expert in your farm.” This discussion revolved around market data, knowing your market stats, and more. This time, we had two top producers demonstrate what they’re doing. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;present-before-paste&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We’ll probably repeat those two topics going forward, but I also want to know what topics you’d like us to discuss.&lt;/strong&gt; Also, what expert agents do you know that would like to be on a future panel? If you have any suggestions, we’d love for you to reach out to us today and let us know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;present-before-paste&quot;&gt;One of the most important things to us at KW is collaboration. &lt;strong&gt;We are happy to collaborate with great agents and would love to collaborate with you in the future.&lt;/strong&gt; If you have any questions for me in the meantime, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 03:35:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/will-you-join-us-for-our-next-mastermind.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/will-you-join-us-for-our-next-mastermind.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lead Follow-Up Made Simple</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/pGYs6izo-qI?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many agents invest adequate time, energy, and resources into lead generation, but fewer take the necessary steps when it comes to lead follow-up. And given how stressful it can be to reach out to leads you’ve already contacted, it’s no wonder why. On top of that, companies like Redfin and Zillow have apps that will automatically follow up with leads, making the playing field even more difficult for agents. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, &lt;strong&gt;Keller Williams will soon be launching a consumer app that has been tested and proven to be preferred above other competing applications. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=When your clients have this app on their phone, you will be instantly positioned as their local expert for all things real estate.%20http://localhost:4000/lead-follow-up-made-simple.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“When your clients have this app on their phone, you will be instantly positioned as their local expert for all things real estate.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In short, not only does Keller Williams provide its agents with a technology-based real estate platform, but it will also soon give them access to a consumer-facing app that makes daunting tasks like lead follow-up much easier.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When your clients have this app on their phone, you will be instantly positioned as their local expert for all things real estate. T&lt;strong&gt;his way, you’ll be at the front of their mind from the moment they’re ready to buy or sell.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 13:46:20 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/lead-follow-up-made-simple.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/lead-follow-up-made-simple.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Deliver Personalized Landing Pages, Generate More Business</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/pYdDTmn8ug4?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you remember, &lt;a href=&quot;https://kwcareerquest.com/how-and-why-to-track-your-tech-related-expenses.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;in my last video,&lt;/a&gt; we talked about how a single technology platform to run your business would save you thousands of dollars and make things much more efficient. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, we’ll examine the pieces of that platform. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first is &lt;strong&gt;personalized landing pages.&lt;/strong&gt; Every agent has a website, but when’s the last time you actually went to a website and logged in? Do you want your buyers and sellers to actually have to go through the process of logging in and looking at the same thing everybody else does when they pull up your website? Of course not—those days are long gone. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do I mean by personalized landing page? On our Keller Williams tech platform, our agents have the ability to send an individual landing page link to each person in their database based on their home address. This link will be based on their specific neighborhood, which we’re already well-acquainted with because of our partnership with Nextdoor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Imagine being able to deliver this personalized landing page to everyone in your database.%20http://localhost:4000/deliver-personalized-landing-pages-generate-more-business.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Imagine being able to deliver this personalized landing page to everyone in your database.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine being able to deliver this personalized landing page to everyone in your database. This page will show them all the activity in their neighborhood and the surrounding ones, allow them to check inventory levels (which are updated every 15 minutes), and enable them to ask questions about their property without requiring them to log in. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all want high rates of customer engagement, right? Well, think about companies with high rates of customer engagement, such as Amazon. They individualize your landing page based on your habits and preferences. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Imagine being able to do the same thing in real estate—deliver neighborhood- and property-specific information to every single person in your database.&lt;/strong&gt; I bet you’d capture a lot more business. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To learn more about our platform, visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://technology.kw.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;technology.kw.com&lt;/a&gt; and surf around. In the meantime, stay tuned for my next video where I’ll discuss the next piece of your technology platform. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, if you have any questions, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d love to help you. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 11:20:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/deliver-personalized-landing-pages-generate-more-business.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/deliver-personalized-landing-pages-generate-more-business.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How (and Why) to Track Your Tech-Related Expenses</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/fjuYxS90HOE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the last episode of our technology series, we discussed what a “platform” is. If you missed that episode, you can find it &lt;a href=&quot;https://kwcareerquest.com/what-separates-a-tech-platform-from-bolt-on-technology.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This time, we’re going to continue our series by talking about the different ways to track your technology-related expenses as an agent. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The amount of money a given agent invests into technology will depend on the way they run their business, as well as how long they’ve been in the industry. &lt;strong&gt;Veteran agents, for example, spend an average of $10,000 on technology.&lt;/strong&gt; This includes video marketing, email campaigns, and many other digital resources. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Every cent you spend should bring you a return in one way or another.%20http://localhost:4000/how-and-why-to-track-your-tech-related-expenses.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Every cent you spend should bring you a return in one way or another.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However much you’re spending on technology right now, you need to be aware of the dollar amount at all times. To do this, write down all the technology-related expenses you can think of in your business, then have your admin staff double check that list. After that, review your credit card statement and see exactly what you’re paying. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you know how much you’re spending, you can then assess whether all of the things you’re investing in are worth it. Every cent you spend should bring you a return in one way or another. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the near future, though, you’ll be able to eliminate many of these expenses altogether, as &lt;strong&gt;Keller Williams is currently rolling out a new end-to-end technology platform that is free to all KW agents. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions about the KW technology platform or about anything else, feel free to give me or my team a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 15:31:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-and-why-to-track-your-tech-related-expenses.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-and-why-to-track-your-tech-related-expenses.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What Separates a Tech Platform From “Bolt-On” Technology?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/L_oaFyqnbIE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome back to the latest installment in our technology series!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today we’ll expand on the &lt;strong&gt;differences between “bolt-on” technology and a technology platform.&lt;/strong&gt; This is an important distinction to make for not only how you run your business, but for your expenses as well. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s important for an agent to harness technology in such a way that it supports your business as opposed to taking your business.&lt;/strong&gt; In our last video, we covered the difference between a technology-enabled agent and an agent enabling technology. If you missed it,&lt;a href=&quot;https://kwcareerquest.com/who-is-the-fiduciary.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; you can check it out here. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Agents across the real estate industry proudly proclaim that their brokerage or company is tech-friendly and, because of this, technology is entirely at their disposal. Much of the technology they’re referring to is “bolt-on.” At 1:00 in the video, you can see the various forms that bolt-on technology takes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An agent who uses technology in this way might have a CRM for their database, along with different mechanisms for their marketing, lead generation, neighborhood research, and maintaining transactions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Later this year, Keller Williams will be unveiling their all-new, all-in-one technology platform.%20http://localhost:4000/what-separates-a-tech-platform-from-bolt-on-technology.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Later this year, Keller Williams will be unveiling their all-new, all-in-one technology platform.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s no surprise that the problem with these technologies is that they tend to be disjointed, independent of one another, and non-communicative and going this route would require multiple databases. You also have to factor in the costs: One could cost $25, another might run $79, and yet another could be $200 per transaction. This can add up quickly for various technologies that don’t communicate. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Later this year, Keller Williams will be unveiling their all-new, all-in-one technology platform as an alternative to this.&lt;/strong&gt; This leading-edge, singular platform will give agents the ability to do everything from lead generation to database management to client maintenance and all things in between. Such a tool will change how we do real estate going forward. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://technology.kw.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;By clicking here&lt;/a&gt;, you can explore the website I’ve mentioned in previous videos and find out how you’ll be able to change the way you run your real estate business through this powerful new technology.     &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, if you have any questions or if you’d like to discuss these developments further, reach out to me anytime. I’d love to have a conversation, and I look forward to meeting you! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 11:26:44 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-separates-a-tech-platform-from-bolt-on-technology.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/what-separates-a-tech-platform-from-bolt-on-technology.html</guid>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who Is The Fiduciary?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/-WxaKWGgj4M?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Fiduciary” is a term you’ve probably heard but may not understand as well as you’d like. The good news is that its meaning is simpler than you might think: A fiduciary is simply the person responsible for a given business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, as you may remember from &lt;a href=&quot;https://kwcareerquest.com/how-technology-has-changed-real-estate-for-good.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;my previous installment in this technology series&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;technology no longer merely helps agents succeed in their business—it’s actually beginning to take business from them.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Technology is now becoming the fiduciary, rather than simply assisting the fiduciary, of real estate businesses with increasing frequency. Sellers who work with these companies don’t select an agent specifically, they simply take what they’re given. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=This shift toward technology as a fiduciary simply indicates a move from technology-enabled agents to agent-enabled technology.%20http://localhost:4000/who-is-the-fiduciary.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“This shift toward technology as a fiduciary simply indicates a move from technology-enabled agents to agent-enabled technology.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t let this scare you, though. The days of technology truly taking over won’t be realized within any of our lifetimes. Agents aren’t going to be replaced entirely. Rather, this shift toward technology as a fiduciary simply indicates a move from technology-enabled agents to agent-enabled technology. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So how do you keep your business within this first category? How do you retain the role of a fiduciary? &lt;strong&gt;The first step you should take is to visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://technology.kw.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://technology.kw.com/&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After you’ve done that, feel free to reach out. If you have any other questions or would like more information, please give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 11:03:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/who-is-the-fiduciary.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/who-is-the-fiduciary.html</guid>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Technology Has Changed Real Estate for Good</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/AoobayYu44Y?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Technology has shaped our modern world, and the real estate industry is no exception. Today I’d like to delve into three key ways real estate is changing as a result:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The MLS is no longer a secret.&lt;/strong&gt; Gone are the days when only real estate professionals had access to the multiple listing service. Today, everyone can see what’s available. Not only that, but with the internet at their fingertips, buyers can easily educate themselves on the real estate process. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;People are doing business on their phones.&lt;/strong&gt; Though it may not be what you’re used to, it’s important to learn to embrace this technology. If I asked 100 real estate agents if they use an app to reach their clients, they may say yes. But if I were to take it a step further and ask those same agents if all of their clients actually use that app as their preferred real estate resource, their answers might not be so consistent. If you can crack the code on making your mobile presence as strong as possible, your business will be more likely to endure into the future. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technology is taking business away from agents.&lt;/strong&gt; You can probably remember at least a few times when a potential client turned down your services in favor of using some online resource instead. This can feel like a punch to the gut, but especially when you realize that these lost clients only constitute a portion of the opportunities you’re missing out on. You need to work with, not against, technology if you want to keep drawing in leads. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=You need to work with, not against, technology if you want to keep drawing in leads.%20http://localhost:4000/how-technology-has-changed-real-estate-for-good.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“You need to work with, not against, technology if you want to keep drawing in leads.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are a ton of resources on this topic, but I believe the best is &lt;a href=&quot;https://technology.kw.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://technology.kw.com/&lt;/a&gt;, where you can learn how to “future proof” your business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any other questions or would like to learn more, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 10:55:23 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-technology-has-changed-real-estate-for-good.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-technology-has-changed-real-estate-for-good.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
