<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Orange County Real Estate Podcast with Jim Crotwell</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://localhost:4000"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Keller Williams Realty Carlsbad - your professional Orange County Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Jim Crotwell</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2019-09-12 15:47:59 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Jim Crotwell</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Orange County, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>JimCrotwell@kw.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Jim Crotwell</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Jim Crotwell</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Orange County, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the Orange County Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Keller Williams Realty Carlsbad - your professional Orange County Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>Keller Williams Command: Built by Agents, for Agents</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/keller-williams-command-built-by-agents-for-agents.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <author>Jim Crotwell</author>
        <pubDate>2019-09-06 11:27:15 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jim+Crotwell/Videos/Are+You+Using+The+Marketing+Feature_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

The way an agent markets themselves is essential to their business, but properly developing and executing one’s marketing strategy isn’t always so simple. This is where Keller Williams Command comes in.

Keller Williams Command is an end-to-end marketing platform built by and for real estate agents. This one-of-a-kind tool utilizes everything agents have been asking for.

One of this platform’s features is Sketchhouse Designs: our marketing warehouse, which allows agents to view, customize, and save designs that can be used on social media, email campaigns, text campaigns, on your website, or ordered for print. This is hugely beneficial, as using consistent designs throughout these various mediums will boost the productivity of your marketing. 

“This platform gives you the tools to reach your database, while also guiding you on the most effective ways to do so.”

Not only does Sketchhouse Designs give you access to all of your marketing designs with just a few clicks, but it also grants you the ability to take advantage of another tool—lead accelerator, which lets you boost designs on social media. Better still, you can do so without paying a middle party. This will give you more clicks and leads for your dollar than on Facebook or Google ads, thanks to the fact that you’re working straight from one convenient source. 

And since the entire Keller Williams Command platform works off of AI, it constantly learns from user input. Over time, the platform records trends on what techniques, marketing mediums, and designs perform the best, and will show you rankings for all of the marketing elements you employ. In short, this platform gives you the tools to reach your database, while also guiding you on the most effective ways to do so. 

You can learn more about this platform, and other pieces of KW technology, by visiting technology.kw.com. 

As always, if you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon. 

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jim+Crotwell/Videos/Are+You+Using+The+Marketing+Feature_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jim+Crotwell/Videos/Are+You+Using+The+Marketing+Feature_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Keller Williams Command is an incredible marketing tool, and today I’d like to explain how it helps agents like you grow their businesses.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jim Crotwell</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Keller Williams Command is an incredible marketing tool, and today I’d like to explain how it helps agents like you grow their businesses.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Orange County, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What “Opportunities” Can Do for You</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-opportunities-can-do-for-you.html</link>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <author>Jim Crotwell</author>
        <pubDate>2019-08-23 08:41:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

What is the new “Opportunities” app in KW Command and what can it do for you?

With Opportunities, you can navigate the first conversation you have with a client all the way to closing and getting paid all on one screen. Also, it calculates pending commission, possible commission, and actual commission based on your true work percentages for your conversion rates from beginning to closing, and it reminds you of follow-ups and tasks and keeps compliance and pay items in the same place. 

The reason so many agents are excited about Opportunities is it enhances the motivation for follow-ups by letting you see the dollar amount attached. While watching the transaction step by step from beginning to end, you can see your money go from potential income to probable income to actual income.

“The reason so many agents are excited about Opportunities is it enhances the motivation for follow-ups by letting you see the dollar amount attached.”

On top of that, it tracks your business (how much of it is listings, how much of it is sales, how much of it is leases, etc.) and where that business comes from. 

If you’d like to test “Opportunities” for yourself and see what it can do, visit Technology.KW.com. If you have any more questions about this app, give us a call and we’d be happy to walk you through it. 

As always, if there’s anything else we can assist you with, feel free to reach out to us as well. We look forward to speaking with you.  
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Why are so many agent excited about our new “Opportunities” app? Find out today.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jim Crotwell</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Why are so many agent excited about our new “Opportunities” app? Find out today.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Orange County, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>We’d Love to See You at Our Upcoming Lead Generation Course</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/wed-love-to-see-you-at-our-upcoming-lead-generation-course.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <author>Jim Crotwell</author>
        <pubDate>2019-08-06 04:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

We’ve got a whole list of events coming up this September, and you won’t want to miss the one I’m unveiling today: On Thursday, September 12, the one and only Gene Rivers will be teaching an all-day course on lead generation. 

If you’re not familiar with Gene and his story, let me fill you in. He has four offices in Florida and along the East Coast with over 500 Keller Williams agents working under him. For more than 20 years, he and his wife have had their own mega-production, top-producing team. He also owns an escrow company as well as an investment company. Now, he spends a lot of his time traveling across the country and teaching at various Keller Williams offices.    

“On September 12, we’ll delve deeper into new ways and strategies to improve your lead generation.”  

This event on September 12 is open to all agents in the area, and we expect a few hundred people to attend. It’ll run from 9 a.m. to 5 p.m. and will be held at The Westin Carlsbad, located at 5480 Grand Pacific Drive. 

Now, let me ask you a question: What was the last class you attended at your office? A contracts class? Perhaps it was a broker update. The reason I ask is that a lot of the material that offices and brokerages teach concerns the transactional side of the business. That’s all well and good, but in my view, there’s a lack of emphasis and education on the business generation side. 

Basically, your business can be broken down into three categories: lead generation, lead follow-up, and transacting. They’re all equally important, but on September 12, we’ll delve deeper into new ways and strategies to improve your lead generation. 

What we won’t do is overwhelm you with 50 different strategies and wish you luck in implementing all of them. We’ll do two things instead: First, we’ll underscore two or three strategies to work into your business, which will help maximize your lead generation. 

Secondly, we’ll talk a lot about follow-up—how to do it and when to do it. If you lack strong follow-up skills, I can guarantee you’re leaving money on the table and missing opportunities for business.  

You can find out more information or register for this event here. 

You’ll receive some information via email from me soon, but in the meantime, make a note of this event on your calendar and reach out to me with any questions you have. I hope to see you there!  

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>The great Gene Rivers joins us on Thursday, September 12, to lead an all-day course on lead generation. Come one, come all!</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jim Crotwell</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>The great Gene Rivers joins us on Thursday, September 12, to lead an all-day course on lead generation. Come one, come all!</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Orange County, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Will You Join Us for Our Next Mastermind?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/will-you-join-us-for-our-next-mastermind.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <author>Jim Crotwell</author>
        <pubDate>2019-07-23 03:35:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jim+Crotwell/Videos/Check+Out+Our+Upcoming+Event.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Today I’d like to just take a moment to tell you about some great panels and other events that we’ve got coming up. 

One is our Top Producer Mastermind, where we invite three or four of our top agents and one outside agent to discuss a monthly topic. These have been really powerful over the last few months. 

The first one we did was about client events and what people are doing in that arena. A few top producers shared what they did, ranging from expensive dinner parties to cheaper events that can still make an impact in the community. 

“These masterminds have been really powerful.”

The second mastermind covered the topic: “How to become the local expert in your farm.” This discussion revolved around market data, knowing your market stats, and more. This time, we had two top producers demonstrate what they’re doing. 

We’ll probably repeat those two topics going forward, but I also want to know what topics you’d like us to discuss. Also, what expert agents do you know that would like to be on a future panel? If you have any suggestions, we’d love for you to reach out to us today and let us know.

One of the most important things to us at KW is collaboration. We are happy to collaborate with great agents and would love to collaborate with you in the future. If you have any questions for me in the meantime, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon. 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jim+Crotwell/Videos/Check+Out+Our+Upcoming+Event.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jim+Crotwell/Videos/Check+Out+Our+Upcoming+Event.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>We’ve been hosting some fantastic discussions over the last few months with top agents from around the area. Going forward, we’d love to have your input.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jim Crotwell</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>We’ve been hosting some fantastic discussions over the last few months with top agents from around the area. Going forward, we’d love to have your input.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Orange County, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Lead Follow-Up Made Simple</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/lead-follow-up-made-simple.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <author>Jim Crotwell</author>
        <pubDate>2019-06-27 13:46:20 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Many agents invest adequate time, energy, and resources into lead generation, but fewer take the necessary steps when it comes to lead follow-up. And given how stressful it can be to reach out to leads you’ve already contacted, it’s no wonder why. On top of that, companies like Redfin and Zillow have apps that will automatically follow up with leads, making the playing field even more difficult for agents. 

Thankfully, Keller Williams will soon be launching a consumer app that has been tested and proven to be preferred above other competing applications. 

“When your clients have this app on their phone, you will be instantly positioned as their local expert for all things real estate.”

In short, not only does Keller Williams provide its agents with a technology-based real estate platform, but it will also soon give them access to a consumer-facing app that makes daunting tasks like lead follow-up much easier.  

When your clients have this app on their phone, you will be instantly positioned as their local expert for all things real estate. This way, you’ll be at the front of their mind from the moment they’re ready to buy or sell.

If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon. 
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>What if your lead follow-up could be done automatically with a simple piece of software? Now, it can.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jim Crotwell</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>What if your lead follow-up could be done automatically with a simple piece of software? Now, it can.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Orange County, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Deliver Personalized Landing Pages, Generate More Business</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/deliver-personalized-landing-pages-generate-more-business.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
        <author>Jim Crotwell</author>
        <pubDate>2019-06-11 11:20:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jim+Crotwell/Videos/The+Importance+Of+Landing+Pages.mp4</guid>
        <description>

As you remember, in my last video, we talked about how a single technology platform to run your business would save you thousands of dollars and make things much more efficient. 

Now, we’ll examine the pieces of that platform. 

The first is personalized landing pages. Every agent has a website, but when’s the last time you actually went to a website and logged in? Do you want your buyers and sellers to actually have to go through the process of logging in and looking at the same thing everybody else does when they pull up your website? Of course not—those days are long gone. 

What do I mean by personalized landing page? On our Keller Williams tech platform, our agents have the ability to send an individual landing page link to each person in their database based on their home address. This link will be based on their specific neighborhood, which we’re already well-acquainted with because of our partnership with Nextdoor.

“Imagine being able to deliver this personalized landing page to everyone in your database.”

Imagine being able to deliver this personalized landing page to everyone in your database. This page will show them all the activity in their neighborhood and the surrounding ones, allow them to check inventory levels (which are updated every 15 minutes), and enable them to ask questions about their property without requiring them to log in. 

We all want high rates of customer engagement, right? Well, think about companies with high rates of customer engagement, such as Amazon. They individualize your landing page based on your habits and preferences. 

Imagine being able to do the same thing in real estate—deliver neighborhood- and property-specific information to every single person in your database. I bet you’d capture a lot more business. 

To learn more about our platform, visit technology.kw.com and surf around. In the meantime, stay tuned for my next video where I’ll discuss the next piece of your technology platform. 

As always, if you have any questions, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d love to help you.  

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jim+Crotwell/Videos/The+Importance+Of+Landing+Pages.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Jim+Crotwell/Videos/The+Importance+Of+Landing+Pages.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Personalized landing pages should be the first piece of your technology platform. Here’s how they benefit you and your customers.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jim Crotwell</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Personalized landing pages should be the first piece of your technology platform. Here’s how they benefit you and your customers.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Orange County, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How (and Why) to Track Your Tech-Related Expenses</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-and-why-to-track-your-tech-related-expenses.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <author>Jim Crotwell</author>
        <pubDate>2019-05-21 15:31:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

In the last episode of our technology series, we discussed what a “platform” is. If you missed that episode, you can find it here.  

This time, we’re going to continue our series by talking about the different ways to track your technology-related expenses as an agent. 

The amount of money a given agent invests into technology will depend on the way they run their business, as well as how long they’ve been in the industry. Veteran agents, for example, spend an average of $10,000 on technology. This includes video marketing, email campaigns, and many other digital resources. 

“Every cent you spend should bring you a return in one way or another.”

However much you’re spending on technology right now, you need to be aware of the dollar amount at all times. To do this, write down all the technology-related expenses you can think of in your business, then have your admin staff double check that list. After that, review your credit card statement and see exactly what you’re paying. 

Once you know how much you’re spending, you can then assess whether all of the things you’re investing in are worth it. Every cent you spend should bring you a return in one way or another. 

In the near future, though, you’ll be able to eliminate many of these expenses altogether, as Keller Williams is currently rolling out a new end-to-end technology platform that is free to all KW agents. 

If you have any other questions about the KW technology platform or about anything else, feel free to give me or my team a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon. 

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>As an agent, how much are you spending on technology? Today, I’ll share a few tips on tracking technology-related expenses, as well as how you can cut back on them.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jim Crotwell</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>As an agent, how much are you spending on technology? Today, I’ll share a few tips on tracking technology-related expenses, as well as how you can cut back on them.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Orange County, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Separates a Tech Platform From “Bolt-On” Technology?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-separates-a-tech-platform-from-bolt-on-technology.html</link>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <author>Jim Crotwell</author>
        <pubDate>2019-05-07 11:26:44 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Welcome back to the latest installment in our technology series!

Today we’ll expand on the differences between “bolt-on” technology and a technology platform. This is an important distinction to make for not only how you run your business, but for your expenses as well. 

It’s important for an agent to harness technology in such a way that it supports your business as opposed to taking your business. In our last video, we covered the difference between a technology-enabled agent and an agent enabling technology. If you missed it, you can check it out here. 

Agents across the real estate industry proudly proclaim that their brokerage or company is tech-friendly and, because of this, technology is entirely at their disposal. Much of the technology they’re referring to is “bolt-on.” At 1:00 in the video, you can see the various forms that bolt-on technology takes. 

An agent who uses technology in this way might have a CRM for their database, along with different mechanisms for their marketing, lead generation, neighborhood research, and maintaining transactions. 

“Later this year, Keller Williams will be unveiling their all-new, all-in-one technology platform.”

It’s no surprise that the problem with these technologies is that they tend to be disjointed, independent of one another, and non-communicative and going this route would require multiple databases. You also have to factor in the costs: One could cost $25, another might run $79, and yet another could be $200 per transaction. This can add up quickly for various technologies that don’t communicate. 

Later this year, Keller Williams will be unveiling their all-new, all-in-one technology platform as an alternative to this. This leading-edge, singular platform will give agents the ability to do everything from lead generation to database management to client maintenance and all things in between. Such a tool will change how we do real estate going forward. 

By clicking here, you can explore the website I’ve mentioned in previous videos and find out how you’ll be able to change the way you run your real estate business through this powerful new technology.     

As always, if you have any questions or if you’d like to discuss these developments further, reach out to me anytime. I’d love to have a conversation, and I look forward to meeting you! 

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>“Bolt-on” technology and tech platforms are two different ways that agents manage their business, and the latter can have a game-changing effect on yours.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jim Crotwell</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>“Bolt-on” technology and tech platforms are two different ways that agents manage their business, and the latter can have a game-changing effect on yours.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Orange County, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Who Is The Fiduciary?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/who-is-the-fiduciary.html</link>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <author>Jim Crotwell</author>
        <pubDate>2019-04-23 11:03:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jim+Crotwell/Videos/Who+Is+The+Fiduciary+In+Your+Real+Estate+Business_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

“Fiduciary” is a term you’ve probably heard but may not understand as well as you’d like. The good news is that its meaning is simpler than you might think: A fiduciary is simply the person responsible for a given business.

However, as you may remember from my previous installment in this technology series, technology no longer merely helps agents succeed in their business—it’s actually beginning to take business from them.

Technology is now becoming the fiduciary, rather than simply assisting the fiduciary, of real estate businesses with increasing frequency. Sellers who work with these companies don’t select an agent specifically, they simply take what they’re given. 

“This shift toward technology as a fiduciary simply indicates a move from technology-enabled agents to agent-enabled technology.”

Don’t let this scare you, though. The days of technology truly taking over won’t be realized within any of our lifetimes. Agents aren’t going to be replaced entirely. Rather, this shift toward technology as a fiduciary simply indicates a move from technology-enabled agents to agent-enabled technology. 

So how do you keep your business within this first category? How do you retain the role of a fiduciary? The first step you should take is to visit https://technology.kw.com/. 

After you’ve done that, feel free to reach out. If you have any other questions or would like more information, please give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jim+Crotwell/Videos/Who+Is+The+Fiduciary+In+Your+Real+Estate+Business_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jim+Crotwell/Videos/Who+Is+The+Fiduciary+In+Your+Real+Estate+Business_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Technology is increasingly taking the role of the fiduciary within real estate businesses, and we’d like to discuss what this means for you today.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jim Crotwell</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Technology is increasingly taking the role of the fiduciary within real estate businesses, and we’d like to discuss what this means for you today.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Orange County, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Technology Has Changed Real Estate for Good</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-technology-has-changed-real-estate-for-good.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
        <author>Jim Crotwell</author>
        <pubDate>2019-04-09 10:55:23 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Technology has shaped our modern world, and the real estate industry is no exception. Today I’d like to delve into three key ways real estate is changing as a result:


  The MLS is no longer a secret. Gone are the days when only real estate professionals had access to the multiple listing service. Today, everyone can see what’s available. Not only that, but with the internet at their fingertips, buyers can easily educate themselves on the real estate process.  
  People are doing business on their phones. Though it may not be what you’re used to, it’s important to learn to embrace this technology. If I asked 100 real estate agents if they use an app to reach their clients, they may say yes. But if I were to take it a step further and ask those same agents if all of their clients actually use that app as their preferred real estate resource, their answers might not be so consistent. If you can crack the code on making your mobile presence as strong as possible, your business will be more likely to endure into the future.  
  Technology is taking business away from agents. You can probably remember at least a few times when a potential client turned down your services in favor of using some online resource instead. This can feel like a punch to the gut, but especially when you realize that these lost clients only constitute a portion of the opportunities you’re missing out on. You need to work with, not against, technology if you want to keep drawing in leads. 


“You need to work with, not against, technology if you want to keep drawing in leads.”

There are a ton of resources on this topic, but I believe the best is https://technology.kw.com/, where you can learn how to “future proof” your business.

If you have any other questions or would like to learn more, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon. 
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Technology has changed the real estate landscape in many ways, and today I’d like to share just three of the most prominent examples of this.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jim Crotwell</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Technology has changed the real estate landscape in many ways, and today I’d like to share just three of the most prominent examples of this.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Orange County, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Playing ‘Red Light, Green Light’ With Your Finances</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/playing-red-light-green-light-with-your-finances.html</link>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <author>Jim Crotwell</author>
        <pubDate>2019-02-28 09:06:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

 

By playing ‘red light, green light,’ I’m referring to managing expenses, which is one of the most important things you can do in a shifting market.

Here at Keller Williams, we have a formula and a tool to manage your expenses and re-margin your business by analyzing where you’re spending money. We teach our agents that for every single dollar you spend, you should expect a return on investment, and if you’re not getting that return, either shift those expenses or stop them altogether. This is what is known as playing ‘red light, green light.’

“It’s a fantastic tool, but not enough agents are utilizing it like they should.”

Based on the experiences of our producing agents locally and around the country, we know what areas need to be red and what areas need to be green. We share that information with our agents and coach them on those areas because we know that you can’t build your business just by cutting expenses; you have to continue your lead generation. You can, however, find your profit and protect it by playing ‘red light, green light.’ It’s a fantastic tool, but not enough agents are utilizing it like they should.

If you’d like a free copy of Gary Keller’s “Shift,” click here. For any other questions you may have, feel free to reach out to me. I’d be glad to have a conversation with you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Today I’ll address a topic from Gary Keller’s book “Shift”: playing ‘red light, green light.’</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jim Crotwell</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Today I’ll address a topic from Gary Keller’s book “Shift”: playing ‘red light, green light.’</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Orange County, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Makes Agent Support at Keller Williams So Different?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-makes-agent-support-at-keller-williams-so-different.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <author>Jim Crotwell</author>
        <pubDate>2019-02-15 10:04:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Agent support is among the most important resources a real estate professional has to draw on in their career—and I’m not talking about the kind of limited support offered to most agents out there. Instead, I’m talking about the sort of top-tier support that helps agents gain momentum in the industry.

It doesn’t matter if an agent has been in the business for 10 days or 10 years—they still need support in order to get to the next level.

Allow me to introduce you to the Agent Leadership Council (ALC). Every Keller Williams market center, the Carlsbad location included, selects eight, nine, or 10 of its top agents each year to serve on the ALC. These agents then get together once per month in order to help run their market center.

“We are all in this together.”

Keller Williams market centers are intrinsically agent-centric, given that they are literally run by their agents. There are three offerings that the ALC employs to run their market centers that I believe to be most impactful:


  The monthly masterminds. Imagine what it would do for your business if you were able to learn directly from your market center’s top-producing agents.
  The Ignite Program. This 12-session jumpstart program has played a major role in helping Keller Williams maintain its status as the No. 1 training company in the world.
  Our open-door policy. Every agent within the Keller Williams Carlsbad market center has an open-door policy, meaning that they are always there to provide support, offer advice, and answer questions.


The bottom line is that Keller Williams offers a culture of collaboration. We are all in this together.

If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>What does real agent support look like? Allow me to share my thoughts on this with you today.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jim Crotwell</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>What does real agent support look like? Allow me to share my thoughts on this with you today.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Orange County, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Are You Coming to KW Family Reunion?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/are-you-coming-to-kw-family-reunion.html</link>
        
          <category>Reviews and Referrals</category>
        
        <author>Jim Crotwell</author>
        <pubDate>2019-01-25 14:50:14 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Keller Williams Family Reunion is right around the corner and I am so excited for it. The problem with most real estate conventions, in general, is that the focus tends to drift away from lead generation and toward selling products or systems that don’t get to the heart of building a business.

At KW Family Reunion, the event is completely organized around the top agents sharing their best practices. I’ve gone every year for the last nine years and I’ll be in New Orleans for this year’s conference.

There are going to be about 15,000 agents from across the country here, and they’ll be bringing some great energy and great information. The week is organized into “breakout sessions” and attendees have to pick and choose which presentations they’re going to attend. It’s fun to go with a team because then you can be in two places at once and come together later to share what you’ve learned.

“If you haven’t signed up yet, it’s not too late.”

In addition, Gary Keller is back as CEO and giving a keynote speech. All of the keynote speakers are going to be focused on talking about the technology that KW is coming out with. I’m excited to attend, take notes, and learn more about how to build my business.

If you haven’t signed up for KW Family Reunion yet, but you’re interested in going, it’s not too late. Reach out to me today and we can help you get out there. If you can’t make it, don’t worry—I’ll be happy to share what I’ve learned with you when I get back.

If you have any more questions for me in the meantime, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Keller Williams Family Reunion is right around the corner. Here’s what you need to know about the event.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jim Crotwell</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Keller Williams Family Reunion is right around the corner. Here’s what you need to know about the event.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Orange County, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>KW Has Revolutionized Home Searching for Both Agents and Consumers</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/kw-has-revolutionized-home-searching-for-both-agents-and-consumers.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <author>Jim Crotwell</author>
        <pubDate>2019-01-14 10:07:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Searching for homes on mobile devices is all the rage nowadays, and it has become quite clear that if you’re not in front of your customers from the get-go, not just from when they want to look at houses, you’re going to lose business. So how do we as agents make sure that we’re in a position to stay connected with our clients at all times?

This January, Keller Williams is rolling out an all-new consumer app available on both mobile devices and desktop computers. This is like nothing they’ve ever seen before from a brokerage, and I’m super excited to help our agents get up and running with this new tech.

“If you’re not in front of your customers from the get-go, not just from when they want to look at houses, you’re going to lose business.”

We fully expect this to be the preferred consumer experience; the app has been introduced to focus groups all over the country over the last six to nine months, and we’ve been developing it intensely these past two years.

I encourage you to pay attention to your email and to take me up on one of our mastermind meetings to really see what’s going on with this Keller Williams mobile search app. It’s designed to help you, the real estate agent, stay in charge of your business and deliver the No. 1 consumer experience.

If you have any questions or would like more information about this app, feel free to reach out to me.

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>oday I’ll discuss how technology and real estate have intersected to deliver our clients the optimal home search experience.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jim Crotwell</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>oday I’ll discuss how technology and real estate have intersected to deliver our clients the optimal home search experience.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Orange County, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Connecting Agents With Clients Through Our Upcoming Systems</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/connecting-agents-with-clients-through-our-upcoming-systems.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
          <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
        <author>Jim Crotwell</author>
        <pubDate>2018-12-26 11:35:50 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>
 

We’ve all felt the impact that technology has made on our lives, and the real estate world is no different. Going into 2019, however, technology is impacting the industry in a way it never has before—in a way that could actually be causing you to lose business.

What we’re going to see going forward are two types of agents: agents who use technology, and technology that uses agents. We at Keller Williams see technology as a valuable resource to use, but not one that should control our professionals altogether.

There are three things we’ll be rolling out in early 2019:


  KW.com and mobile search app. These will help connect the consumer with properties and agents.
  KW Command. This connects the consumer to the agent.
  KW Connect. This connects the agent to their market center or brokerage.


All three of these are integrated into one system that will help agents work and run their business—from the original home search all the way to closing a transaction.

“We at Keller Williams see technology as a valuable resource to use.”

If you’re not with Keller Williams and want to know what this upcoming technology can do for your business, keep an eye on your email over the next few months. We’ll be sharing with you monthly masterminds with top agents who have implemented these tools in their businesses.

If you have any questions or would like more information, feel free to reach out to me. I look forward to helping you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Keller Williams is introducing a new, integrated system to help connect agents with agents.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jim Crotwell</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Keller Williams is introducing a new, integrated system to help connect agents with agents.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Orange County, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Let Us Help You Plan Your Business in 2019</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/let-us-help-you-plan-your-business-in-2019.html</link>
        
          <category>Listing Presentation</category>
        
        <author>Jim Crotwell</author>
        <pubDate>2018-12-07 10:49:50 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

As we come to the end of the year, real estate agents all over the area will be getting their business plans in place for 2019. People tend to put a lot of energy into building these plans, but then they put them away and don’t look at them again until the end of the year.

We do things a little bit differently here at Keller Williams with our GPS plan. It’s a living business plan. I’ve taught this plan in plenty of places all over Southern California and I’m doing it again in Carlsbad on December 18.

It’s called “Reset and Recharge” and it’s the perfect time to plan your business for 2019, especially in this shifting market.

“Debunking these myths will really help get your mind in the right place.”

We’ll cover many different topics in the meeting, including the 7 myth understandings of real estate. One of them is the idea that “This won’t work in my market” for whatever reason. Another is “I can’t accomplish that because I don’t have enough time.” Debunking these myths will really help get your mind in the right place. That is so important because I firmly believe that your mindset is 80% of your success in your business.

This is just a short preview of what you’ll learn in the “Reset and Recharge” event. The last time we did this, the agents on our team saw huge success. Within 45 days, we had three active listings and four buyer escrows from those agents that directly correlated with their GPS business plan.

If you have any questions about the event in the meantime, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I hope to see you there!

 
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>We’d love to help you get ready for 2019 at our upcoming “Reset and Recharge” event. Here’s what you’ll learn by attending.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jim Crotwell</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>We’d love to help you get ready for 2019 at our upcoming “Reset and Recharge” event. Here’s what you’ll learn by attending.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Orange County, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The 3 Types of Agents Found During Market Shifts</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-3-types-of-agents-found-during-market-shifts.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
          <category>Listing Presentation</category>
        
        <author>Jim Crotwell</author>
        <pubDate>2018-11-25 01:58:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

The markets all over California are undergoing a shift, including here in San Diego and North County.

In Gary Keller’s book “The Shift: How Top Agents Tackle Tough Times,” Gary teaches us that there are three types of real estate agents that tend to show up when the market shifts:

1. The pessimist. This is the agent who thinks that their career is changing, their business is changing, and that real estate is too hard—market shifts cause these agents to rethink their careers altogether.

2. The optimist. The optimistic agent is in denial about what’s happening in the market with regards to prices, interest rates, days on market, and so on. They think that the market will suddenly return to how it was a year ago. The optimist isn’t paying attention to the actual numbers, stats, and data—they’re ostriches with their heads in the sand.

3. The realist. The realist plans for a market shift, but also studies and implements models, systems, and tools that are proven by top agents.

Clearly, I recommend approaching the shifting market with a realist’s attitude.

“The last time we had a shift in the market about 10 years ago, Keller Williams was the No. 4 real estate company in the nation. We emerged from that shift as the No. 1 company.”

Here’s an interesting statistic: The last time we had a shift in the market about 10 years ago, Keller Williams was the No. 4 real estate company in the nation. We emerged from that shift as the No. 1 company. That means those realist agents, who studied proven models and systems, were attracted to our business and succeeded by joining us.

That period was a lot like today—the market is shifting again. With that in mind, I want to invite you to come pick up a free copy of “The Shift.” I’d be happy to share it with you, and when you’ve read it, we can talk about it further, if you’d like. There are actually 12 tactics to engage in during the shift and see it less as a scary market change and more as what we call “the gift of the shift.”If you would like a free copy of “The Shift” or you have any other questions, feel free to reach out and contact me. I look forward to speaking with you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Today I wanted to discuss the book “The Shift.” It is extremely important in relation to what’s going on in our current market.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jim Crotwell</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Today I wanted to discuss the book “The Shift.” It is extremely important in relation to what’s going on in our current market.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Orange County, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Welcome To My Blog!</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/welcome-to-my-blog.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
          <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
          <category>Listing Presentation</category>
        
        <author>Jim Crotwell</author>
        <pubDate>2018-11-14 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>My mission on this blog site is to provide you with the necessary lead generation and technology tools to, in turn, provide buyers and sellers in Southern California with the highest quality and most professional real estate services possible. 

I have a strong grasp of the Southern California real estate market and how it can directly affect you and your business.

So, I plan to post two educational messages a month that will give you insight into strategies and systems to help you better grow your business and how you, as an agent, can benefit from joining a team like ours.

Check back because content will be coming soon!
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type=""/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Learn how to advance your career in real estate with my tips, tools, and insight into the market.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jim Crotwell</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Learn how to advance your career in real estate with my tips, tools, and insight into the market.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Orange County, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Jim Crotwell</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Jim Crotwell</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Keller Williams Realty Carlsbad - your professional Orange County Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
